Pietro Belluschi Papers
Pietro Belluschi Papers
- Architectural projects, numbered
  - 1222 Paul Boley House Alterations, Oswego, OR [Residential], 1950
    - Correspondence (Box 190)
    - Drawings (Tube 453)
  - 1223 Pacific Building Toilet Room Ventilation [Commercial]
    - Correspondence (Box 190)
  - 1224 Mark E. Hoehne House, Longview, WA [Residential]
    - Correspondence (Box 190)
  - 1225 Benson Hotel elevators [Residential]
    - Correspondence (Box 190)
  - 1226 Wilson Lumber Co. Office, Warm Springs, OR [Commercial], 1951
    - Correspondence (Box 190)
    - Drawings (Tube 453)
    - Photographs, 1 item (Drawer 8 / 1)
  - 1227 Curators Residence, Champoeg State Park, Champoeg, OR [Residential], 1953
    - Drawings (Tube 466)
    - Renderings and hardback sketches, 1 item (Drawer 9 / 3)
  - 1228 J.B. Stewart /Steward Residence, St. Helens, OR [Residential], 1931
    - Correspondence (Box 190)
    - Drawings (Tube 465)
    - Photographs, 1 item (Drawer 8 / 2)
    - Specifications (Box 453)
  - 1229 U. S. National Bank Lunchroom [Commercial]
    - Correspondence (Box 190)
    - Shop drawings (Box 430)
  - 1230 Meade Building Alterations, Portland, OR [Commercial], 1951
    - Correspondence, cornice alterations (Box 190)
    - Drawings, 1 sheet (Tube 453)
  - 1231 U. S. Army, Eielson Air Force Base, Indoor Training Facility [Government]
    - Correspondence (Box 190)
    - Shop drawings (Box 430)
  - 1232 Citizen's Branch, Safety Deposit Lobby Alterations, Portland, OR [Commercial], 1951
    - Correspondence (Box 190)
    - Drawings (Tube 454)
  - 1726 First Methodist Church, Duluth, MN [Religious], 1965
    - Drawings (Tube 745)
    - Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 463)
  - 1933 Baltimore Life Insurance Company - Original building, site plan, Baltimore, MD [Commercial], 1959-1965
    - Drawings (Tube 875)
  - 2605 [unknown]
    - Specifications (Box 453)
  - 3016 Worcester Center, Worcester, MA [Commercial], 1970
    - Drawings (Tube 732)
  - 4103 Goucher College, Towson, MD [Educational], 1959-1960
    - Drawings, surveys, auditorium, site grading (Tube 788)
  - 4144 Goucher College, Towson, MD [Educational], 1959-1960
    - Drawings, surveys, auditorium, site grading (Tube 788)
  - 5503 Peabody Institute, Towson Branch, Towson, MD [Institutional], 1957
    - Drawings (Tube 837)
  - 5705 Church and Monastery for the Order of Saint Benedict, Portsmouth, RI [Religious], 1938
    - Drawings (Tube 851)
    - Drawings (Tube 852)
  - 6125 May Memorial Unitarian Church, Syracuse, NY [Religious], 1962-1963
    - Drawings, blueprints (Tube 827)
    - Drawings, preliminary drawings and renderings (Tube 828)
    - Drawings, plans (Tube 870)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 467)
  - 6301 Equitable Savings and Loan Association, Portland, OR [Commercial], 1963
    - Drawings, part 1 of blueprints (Tube 814)
    - Drawings, part 2 of blueprints, plaza landscaping (Tube 815)
    - Drawings, lower levels, garage (Tube 816)
    - Drawings, 1952; 1963; also lists job #15034 (Tube 817)
    - Drawings, remodel prelim (Tube 824)
    - Drawings, remodel prelim, prelim elevation, directory board (Tube 825)
  - 6608 Clark Art Institute, Williamstown, MA [Museum], 1966-1969
    See also Correspondence-subject files, 1991 accession: Clark Art Institute.
    - Drawings (Tube 746)
    - Drawings, 1967-1969 (Tube 747)
    - Drawings, 1968 (Tube 794)
    - Drawings, 1968 (Tube 795)
    - Drawings, 1967-1968; elevations and floor plans (Tube 819)
    - Drawings, 1966-1968; miscellaneous plans, sketches, site plans (Tube 820)
    - Drawings, 1968; blueprints (Tube 832)
    - Drawings, 1968; blueprints (Tube 833)
    - Drawings, 1969; final review set (Tube 882)
    - Drawings, 1969-1970; plumbing, foundation, air, sprinklers (Tube 883)
  - 6408 Portland Art Museum, Art School Addition, Portland, OR [Museum], 1966
    - Drawings (Tube 764)
    - Drawings (Tube 765)
  - 6716 Colonial Estates, Springfield, MA [Residential], 1969
    - Drawings (Tube 725)
    - Drawings (Tube 916)
    - Drawings (Tube 920)
- Architectural projects, unnumbered
  Material in this series is listed alphabetically by job title. In some cases, additional material relating to a client or building may also be found in the preceding series, "Architectural projects, numbered."
  - 20 State St Tower, Boston, MA [Commercial], 1966
    - Drawings (Tube 909)
  - 225 Congress St, 31 Story Office Building, Boston, MA [Commercial], 1968-1973
    - Drawings (Tube 806)
    - Drawings, 1968 (Tube 842)
    - Drawings, 1968 (Tube 843)
    - Plans, 1968 (Tube 890)
    - Plans, 1968-1973 (Tube 900)
    - Plans, elevations, 1969 (Tube 891)
    - Plans, elevations, drawings, 1968-1969 (Tube 892)
  - J. C. Ainsworth Residence Alterations [Residential]
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 6)
  - Akron Public Library [Library]
    - Miscellaneous (Box 459)
  - H. R. Albee
    - Drawings, preliminary sketches (Drawer MCD 8)
  - Allied Bazaar, Portland Aud., Portland, OR [Commercial]
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 6)
  - Aluminum Building, I Street, Washington, DC [Other], 1967
    - Drawings (Tube 836)
    - Drawings (Tube 525)
  - American Bank Building [Commercial]
    - Renderings and hardback sketches (Drawer 8 / 3)
  - American Bank Building, Portland OR [Commercial], could be any one of several bank jobs
    - Photographs, includes photo of American Bank and Trust Co. in New Orleans, possibly a reference photo (Box 532)
    - Photographs (Oversize 5)
  - American Express [Commercial]
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 17)
  - American Mail and Dollar Steamshipline (tenant change), Portland, OR [Commercial], 1927
    - Drawings (Tube 463)
  - American Safety Razor [Commercial]
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 25)
  - American Standard [Commercial]
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 23)
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 24)
  - Anita Shops
    - Renderings and hardback sketches (Drawer 8 / 4; 8 / 5)
  - Apartment Building, Pendleton, OR [Residential]
    - Drawings, fronts (Drawer MCD 6)
  - Apartment Building, King and Park, Pendleton, OR [Residential]
    - Renderings and hardback sketches, 1 item (Drawer 9 / 3)
  - Arlington Club [Institutional]
    - Drawings, sketches for bar-room alterations (Drawer MCD 6)
    - Drawings (Tube 305)
    - Drawings (Tube 306)
  - Armishaw Bros. and Ed Clapp Shoe Co. [Commercial], 1928
    - Drawings (Tube 463)
  - I. Aronson Jewelry Store [Commercial]
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 8)
  - Artist's residence, Portland, OR [Residential]
    - Renderings and hardback sketches, 1 item (Drawer 9 / 3)
  - G. E. Atiyeh Residence [Residential]
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 39)
  - Atkinson Elementary School [Educational]
    - Photographs, 4 folders (Box 532)
  - Automotive Division, State of Oregon [Commercial], 1946
    - Drawings, for building (Tube 463)
  - Bakelite Corp. [Commercial]
    - Drawings, design of offices using Bakelite products (Drawer MCD 3)
  - Baltimore Civic Center proposal [Other]
    - Miscellaneous (Box 459)
  - Baltimore Concert Hall, Baltimore, MD [Other], 1977
    - Drawings, check set (Tube 789)
  - Baltimore County Government Center, Towson, MD [Government], 1968
    - Drawings (Tube 829)
    - Drawings (Tube 830)
    - Drawings (Tube 831)
  - Baltimore Life Insurance Company / United States Fidelity and Guaranty Co, Baltimore, MD [Commercial], 1967
    - Drawings (Tube 811)
    - Drawings (Tube 876)
  - Bancroft Commons (50 Franklin St.) Alterations and Additions, Samuel Glaser Ass., Worcester, MA [Residential], 1963
    - Reference material (Tube 918)
  - Bank of America World Headquarters, San Francisco, CA [Commercial], 1964
    - Drawings (Tube 804)
    - Drawings and elevations (Tube 887)
    - Floor plans and elevations (Tube 896)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 459)
  - Bank of California [Commercial]
    See also Job 408 and Job 1055.
    - Renderings and hardback sketches, 11 items (Drawer 8 / 3)
  - Bank and Office Buildings, 6th Street, Portland, OR [Commercial]
    - Drawings, miscellaneous (Tube 464)
  - Bank of Toppenish [Commercial]
    - Drawings, tracings from the office of Doyle and Merriam (Tube 527)
  - Bankers Trust Building, New York, NY [Commercial], 1961
    - Drawings (Tube 909)
  - L. R. Banks Summer House, Oak Grove, OR [Residential]
    - Drawings (Drawer SD 8)
    - Drawings, garage, solarium (Drawer SD 8)
  - Bay Ocean Hotel [Residential]
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 6)
  - Baystate West, Springfield, MA [Commercial], 1967-1968
    See also Correspondence-subject files, 1991 accession: Baystate West.
    - Drawings (Tube 834)
    - Drawings (Tube 840)
    - Drawings (Tube 841)
    - Drawings (Tube 906)
  - Beals Building, Tillamook, OR [Commercial]
    - Drawings (Drawer SD 5)
  - F. Beck Residence [Residential]
    - Drawings, house sketches (Drawer MCD 6)
  - Bedell Building [Commercial], 1925
    - Photographs (Box 533)
  - Frank Belvail Residence, Pendleton, OR [Residential]
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 6)
  - Bennington College Library, Bennington, VT [Library]
    - Miscellaneous (Box 460)
  - Benson Hotel, Old Oregon, Portland, OR [Residential], 1912
    See Job 142.
  - Charles Berg Store Alterations [Commercial]
    - Drawings (Drawer SD 8)
  - G. G. Bingham Residence [Residential]
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 25)
  - Blacksmith Cresent Public School, North York, Ontario [Educational], 1967
    - Drawings (Tube 921)
  - Block Development, Yamhill, OR [Urban Planning], 1944
    - Drawings (Tube 459)
  - Blodgett, Portland, OR [Commercial], 1927
    - Preliminary drawings of office building (Tube 464)
  - Blossom Music Center Pavilion, Cleveland, OH [Other], 1967
    - Correspondence (Box 460)
    - Drawings (Tube 782)
    - Drawings (Tube 783)
  - Board of Trade Building [Other]
    - Drawings, revolving doors (Drawer MCD 4)
  - Booth Property Parking lot, Skidmore Owings & Merrill [Other]
    - Drawings (Tube 464)
  - Boston campus, University of Massachusetts [Educational]
    - Miscellaneous, design review (Box 460)
  - Boston City Hall, Boston, MA [Government], 1963
    - Drawings (Tube 839)
  - Boston Company Building, Boston, MA [Commercial], 1968
    - Drawings (Tube 780)
    - Drawings (Tube 894)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 460)
  - Boston, Downtown, Boston, MA [Urban Planning], 1966-1977
    - Drawings, auto, bus, goods traffic patterns (Tube 901)
  - Boston North, Boston, MA [Urban Planning], 1986
    - Drawings, illustrative concept plan (Tube 895)
  - J. L. Bowman Hotel at Camp Arrah Wanna, Welches, OR [Residential]
    - Drawings (Drawer SD 5)
  - Boy Scout Headquarters [Institutional]
    - Drawings (Drawer SD 7)
  - W. L. Brewster [Residential]
    - Drawings, alterations to house (Drawer SD 4)
    - Drawings, warehouse (Drawer SD 4)
    - Drawings, house (Drawer SD 7)
  - Broadway Dyers and Cleaners Building [Commercial]
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 7)
  - Broadway and Oak St. [unnamed building], Portland, OR [Other], 1932
    - Drawings (Tube 464)
  - Brockton Housing, Pine Grove, Brockton, MA [Residential], 1970
    - Drawings (Tube 787)
  - E. C. Bronaugh
    - Drawings, stables (Drawer SD 7)
  - Brooklyn Museum Italian Exhibit, Brooklyn, NY [Museum]
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 24)
  - Brooksales, Inc. Offices [Commercial]
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 25)
  - Sam H. Brown Apartments [Residential]
    - Drawings (Drawer SD 5)
  - Brownsville Woollen Mills Store Alterations [Commercial]
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 25)
  - Frank Bruhn Residence [Residential]
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 6)
  - Building at Lownsdale & Washington [Commercial]
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 8)
  - Bungalow in front of water tower [Residential]
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 40)
  - Charles F. Burg Residence Alterations [Residential]
    - Drawings (Drawer SD 8)
  - Louis Burke Residence [Residential]
    - Drawings (Drawer SD 5)
    - Drawings (Drawer SD 6)
  - Burlington Mall Road [Other]
    - Drawings, surveyor's plan (Tube 797)
  - Butler Building, Hood River [Commercial], 1924
    See Job 388.
  - Buyer's Building Alterations [Other]
    - Drawings (Tube 464)
  - Henry Cabell Residence [Residential]
    - Drawings, alterations (Drawer SD 8)
    - Drawings, house (Drawer SD 8)
  - Cambridge Building
    - Drawings, new storefronts (Drawer MCD 25)
    - Drawings (Drawer SD 7)
  - Camp Adainton, Recreation Center for Enlisted Personnel [Government], 1943
    - Drawings, 2 items (Tube 303)
  - Camp Fire Girls Summer Camp, Clackama River, OR [Institutional], 1923
    - Drawings (Drawer SD 4)
    - Drawings (Tube 293)
  - Canadian Bank of Commerce [Commercial]
    - Drawings, proposed building (Drawer SD 3)
    - Renderings and hardback sketches, 1 item (Drawer 8 / 3)
  - Canadian Corp for 1967 World Expo [Exhibition]
    - Drawings (Tube 802)
  - Canadian Legion Convention [Institutional]
    - Drawings, cenotaph (Drawer SD 5)
    - Renderings and hardback sketches, cenotaph; 1 item (Drawer 9 / 5)
  - Cascade Building, Selling [Commercial]
    - Photographs, includes negative (Box 533)
  - Seth Catlin Residence [Residential]
    - Drawings (Drawer SD 6)
  - Cedar Lane Unitarian Church, Bethesda, MD [Religious]
    - Miscellaneous (Box 460)
  - Cedar Realty House [Residential]
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 17)
  - Central National Bank Alterations [Commercial]
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 39)
  - Century City, Los Angeles, CA
    - Miscellaneous (Box 460)
  - Chapel, University of Oklahoma City, Oklahoma City, OK [Religious]
    - Miscellaneous (Box 460)
  - Chapman House [Residential], 1919
    - Miscellaneous plans (Tube 459)
  - Charles H. Greeley Garage [Industrial]
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 40)
  - Charleston Center, Charleston, SC [Other], 1982
    - Drawings (Tube 497)
  - Charlesworth Building, Portland, OR [Other], 1928
    - Drawings (Tube 464)
    - Drawings (Tube 295)
  - Christenson Oil Plant, OR [Industrial], 1944
    - Drawings, 1 sheet - Mt. St. Helen Road (Tube 463)
  - Church of the Christian Union (Unitarian), Rockford, IL [Religious], 1963-1964
    - Drawings, 1964 (Tube 743)
    - Drawings, 1963 (Tube 744)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 460)
  - Church of the Redeemer, Baltimore, MD [Religious], 1955-1957
    - Drawings (Tube 758)
    - Drawings (Tube 759)
    - Drawings, admin, Sunday School wing (Tube 810)
    - Drawings, early sketches, plans, site, landscaping (Tube 874)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 461)
  - Church at Mildura, Victoria, Australia [Religious]
    - Drawings, sketches (Drawer SD 6)
  - Civic Center, Portland, OR [Other], 1943
    - Studies (Tube 295)
  - Clark County National Bank [Commercial], 1944
    - Drawings (Tube 524)
  - Clark Residence Alterations [Residential]
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 8)
  - R. C. Coe Residence, Woodburn, OR [Residential]
    - Drawings (Drawer SD 8)
  - Colonial Stores [Commercial]
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 1)
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 2)
    - Drawings, displays (Drawer MCD 3)
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 19)
    - Drawings, blueprints (Drawer MCD 19)
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 5)
    - Drawings, Standard Supermarket (Drawer MCD 5)
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 21)
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 22)
    - Drawings, framing and pylon (Drawer MCD 22)
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 23)
  - Columbia Point, Boston, MA [Urban Planning]
    - Aerial view (Tube 920)
  - Colombia Theatre Alterations [Other]
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 7)
  - Comfort Stations, Defense Housing Project, Vancouver, WA [Government], 1943
    - Drawings (Tube 294)
  - Commercial Development (proposed), Salem, OR [Commercial], 1953
    - Drawings (Tube 802)
  - Commonwealth Inc. Night Club [Other], 1933
    - Drawings (Tube 463)
  - Commonwealth Trust & Title
    - Renderings and hardback sketches, 1 item (Drawer 8 / 4; 8 / 5)
  - Community Church at Adams OR, Adams, OR [Religious], 1920
    - Drawings (Tube 462)
  - Concordia College, Portland, OR [Educational], 1926
    - Drawings (Tube 304)
  - Continental Oil Co. Service Station [Commercial]
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 2)
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 3)
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 4)
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 21)
    - Drawings, preliminary drawings (Drawer MCD 21)
    - Drawings, perspective study, photostats (Drawer MCD 23)
  - Cooch Building, Parker Schramm [Other], 1942
    - Drawings (Tube 295)
  - Corbett Building, Portland, OR [Commercial], 1908
    - Drawings, 73-A-4; address given as 5th and Stark (Drawer MCD 39)
    - Drawings, 5th and Stark, STS [AH] (Drawer SD 7)
    - Drawings, original tracings (Tube 296)
    - Drawings (Tube 297)
    - Renderings and hardback sketches, lobby; 2 items (Drawer 9 / 4; 9 / 5)
  - Corbett Estate
    - Drawings, additions to dock at foot of Alder St. (Drawer SD 7)
    - Drawings, alterations to Hamilton Building (Drawer SD 7)
    - Drawings, building at corner of 10th and Morrison (Drawer SD 7)
    - Drawings, building at corner of 6th and Pine (Drawer SD 7)
    - Drawings, miscellaneous buildings (Drawer SD 7)
  - E. R. Corbett Residence Alterations [Residential]
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 8)
  - H. L. Corbett Residence Alterations [Residential]
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 8)
  - Cornelius Hotel, Proposed Alterations, Portland, OR [Residential], 1941
    - Drawings (Tube 460)
  - Corvallis High School, Corvallis, OR [Educational]
    - Drawings (Drawer SD 2)
  - Courtney fireplace [Residential]
    - Drawings (Tube 293)
  - Crooker [possibly Crocker?] Residence [Residential]
    - Drawings (Drawer SD 2)
  - Crown-Zellerbach, Proposed Alterations for Pittock Block, Portland, OR [Commercial], 1937
    - Drawings (Tube 463)
  - Daily News Building Dining Room (proposed) [Commercial]
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 1)
  - Daughters of Washington Log Building [Institutional]
    - Drawings (Drawer SD 7)
  - Davidson residence [Residential], 1936
    - Drawings (Tube 292)
  - De Graaf Residence, Proposed addition, Sandy, OR (Portland) [Residential], 1936
    - Drawings (Tube 459)
  - E. J. De Hart Residence [Residential]
    - Drawings, house and stables (Drawer SD 3)
  - Del Monte Corporation headquarters building, San Francisco, CA [Commercial]
    - Miscellaneous (Box 461)
  - Dent Mowrey, Fence and Lattice, Portland, OR [Residential], 1941
    - Drawings (Tube 294)
  - E. L. Devereaux Residence [Residential]
    - Drawings (Drawer SD 1)
  - Dewey Square Office Building, Boston, MA [Commercial]
    - Drawings, 1968 (Tube 738)
    - Drawings, 1970 (Tube 739)
    - Drawings (Tube 846)
    - Drawings (Tube 847)
    - Drawings (Tube 854)
  - Disciples of Christ (Christian), Cedar Hills, OR [Religious], 1987
    - Drawings (Tube 489)
  - Doll House, Junior League, Portland, OR [Other], 1939
    - Drawings (Tube 291)
  - Dorchester, Boston, MA [Urban Planning]
    - Planometric and aerial views (Tube 797)
  - Dormitory Apartments for war workers [Residential], 1942
    - Drawings (Tube 460)
    - Photographs (Drawer 8 / 1)
  - Dormitory, Rhode Island School of Design, Providence, RI [Residential]
    - Miscellaneous (Box 462)
  - Doyle, Portland, OR
    - Drawings, 1927; garden (Tube 291)
    - Drawings, 1938; office layouts (Tube 463)
  - Doyle Cottage, Neah-Kah-Nie, OR [Residential]
    - Drawings (Drawer SD 4)
  - Doyle Family Headstones [Monument]
    - Drawings (Drawer SD 2)
  - Doyle Property, Morrison St.
    - Drawings (Drawer SD 2)
  - A. E. Doyle Residences [Residential]
    - Drawings, 755 Tillamook (Drawer SD 2)
    - Drawings, East 8th St. (Drawer SD 2)
    - Drawings, Portland Heights house (Drawer SD 2)
  - Dr. Jack Residence Alterations, East Moreland [Residential], 1927
    - Drawings (Tube 293)
  - Drake Apartment House, Portland, OR [Residential], 1938
    - Drawings (Tube 457)
  - Dresser Industries [Commercial]
    - Drawings, office plans (Drawer MCD 1)
  - Charles Early Residence [Residential]
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 17)
  - Edergerton, Germeshausen, and Grier Inc. [EG&G defense contractor], Bedford, MA [Commercial], 1963
    - Drawings (Tube 845)
  - T. L. Elliott Building, Hood River, OR [Commercial]
    - Drawings (Drawer SD 6)
  - Ellis-Schiller Co. Garage, Pendleton, OR [Industrial]
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 6)
  - Embarcadero Center, San Francisco Development Agency, San Francisco, CA [Commercial], 1969
    - Drawings (Tube 873)
    - Miscellaneous, Embarcadero Center and Golden Gateway (Box 470)
  - Equitable Savings and Loan Association / Equitable Building, Portland, OR [Commercial], 1946
    - Drawings, blueprints part 2, 45-111 (Tube 849)
    - Drawings, blueprints part 3, 201-320 (Tube 850)
    - Photographs, 7 items (Drawer 8 / 2)
    - Renderings and hardback sketches, 18 items (Drawer 8 / 4; 8 / 5)
    - Miscellaneous, listed as "Equitable Center" (Box 462)
  - Ethyl Walker School, Simsbury, CT [Educational], [1966]
    - Drawings (Tube 726)
  - Eutaw Place Baptist Church, Baltimore, MD [Religious], 1966-1967
    - Drawings (Tube 749)
    - Drawings (Tube 750)
    - Drawings (Tube 751)
    - Working drawings (Tube 752)
    - Working drawings (Tube 753)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 462)
  - Dr. John Evans Residence (proposed), Salem, OR [Residential], 1941
    - Drawings (Tube 291)
  - Everson Museum of Art, Syracuse, NY [Museum], 1963
    - Drawings (Tube 818)
  - H. E. Failing
    - Drawings, dock (Drawer SD 6)
    - Drawings, garage (Drawer SD 5)
    - Drawings, gravestones (Drawer SD 6)
    - Drawings, wardrobe (Drawer SD 5)
  - Federal Office Building, Architectural Competition [Competition]
    - Drawings (Tube 298)
  - Federal Reserve Bank [no location given] [Commercial]
    - Drawings, proposed new building (Drawer SD 4)
  - Federal Reserve Bank, Boston, Boston, MA [Commercial], 1970
    - Drawings (Tube 787)
  - Federal Reserve Bank of Philadelphia, Philadelphia, PA [Commercial]
    - Miscellaneous (Box 462)
  - C. B. Fernald Building on Salmon St. [Commercial], Ladd & Tilton, Agents
    - Drawings (Drawer SD 3)
  - Ferris Apartments, Ketchikan, AK [Residential], 1927
    - Drawings (Tube 457)
  - Firestone Sales and Service Shop
    - Renderings and hardback sketches, 3 items (Drawer 8 / 4; 8 / 5)
  - First Community Church (not built), Columbus, OH [Religious], 1961-1965
    - Miscellaneous (Box 463)
  - First Lutheran Church of Boston [Religious]
    - Miscellaneous (Box 463)
  - First National Bank [no location given] [Commercial]
    - Drawings (Drawer SD 4)
  - First National Bank, Camas, Camas, WA [Commercial], 1930
    - Drawings (Tube 522)
    - Renderings and hardback sketches, 1 item (Drawer 8 / 3)
  - First National Bank, Klamath, Klamath Falls, OR [Commercial]
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 25)
  - First National Bank of Portland, Salem branch, Salem, OR [Commercial]
    - Photographs, 3 items (Drawer 8 / 1)
  - First Presbyterian Church [no location given]
    - Renderings and hardback sketches, 1 item (Drawer 9 / 1; 9 / 2)
  - Fisher & Thorson Store Alterations [Commercial]
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 39)
  - Flat Building, Belmont and 68th, for Philip Hart, Portland, OR [Commercial]
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 39)
  - Folding Chair / Table Combination [Furniture]
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 19)
  - Ford Building [Commercial], 1914
    - Drawings, rotunda (Drawer MCD 23)
    - Photographs (Box 533)
  - Ford Chairs [Furniture]
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 1)
  - Ford Foundation [Institutional]
    - Drawings (Drawer MCD 23)
  - Ford Motor Co., Dearborn, MI [Commercial]
    - Drawings, executive offices (Drawer MCD 2)
    - Drawings, administration building (Drawer MCD 24)
    - Drawings, administration building (Drawer MCD 25)
    - Drawings, Lincoln-Mercury Division office alterations (Drawer MCD 24)
    - Drawings, alterations and additions to Dearborn Inn (Drawer MCD 24)
    - Drawings, courtesy building (Drawer MCD 25)
  - Forest Rangers Cabin at Eagle Creek
    - Drawings (Drawer SD 5)
  - Fort Meyer Post Chapel, Ft. Myers, VA [Religious]
    - Miscellaneous (Box 463)
  - Fort Point Channel Study, Boston, MA [Urban Planning], 1972
    - Drawings (Tube 904)
  - Franks Garage and Monument
    - Drawings (Drawer SD 6)